- This world is beyond cruelty.
♪♪♪
You've been fighting
the Harkonnens for decades.
My family's been
fighting them for centuries.
They were massacred...
alongside my father.
- Your father didn't
believe in revenge.
[shouts]
- We believe in Fremen.
- Let me fight beside you.
- [click]
- Reload!
♪♪♪
- He said that--
- I got that.
Thanks.
- I won't be fighting for him.
I'm fighting for my people.
You young pup.
♪♪♪
- Do you believe in Paul?
- There are signs.
- [cheering]
♪♪♪
- The prophet.
Why is that a bad thing? Use it.
- Because all my visions
lead to horror.
- [gasps]
♪♪♪
- Because you lose control.
- Because I gain it.
- Chani, do you believe in me?
♪♪♪
- Paul Atreides is still alive.
- Deal with this prophet.
- Show me who you are.
[grunting]
- Your father...
♪♪♪
...was a weak man.
- Look who's back from the dead.
♪♪♪
- I will do what must be done.
- We gave them
something to hope for.
- That's not hope!
♪♪♪
Chani!
I will love you
as long as I breathe.
♪♪♪
- This prophecy is
how they enslave us!
♪♪♪
- It's not a prophecy.
It's a story.
- I don't care what you believe!
I believe.
♪♪♪
- I am Paul Muad'dib Atreides!
Duke of Arrakis!
♪♪♪
He who can destroy a thing
has the real control of it.
♪♪♪